{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115814072","data":{"timestamp":" 948115814071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115818281","data":{"timestamp":" 948115818280"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115819834","data":{"timestamp":" 948115819834"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115822917","data":{"timestamp":" 948115822917"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115824492","data":{"timestamp":" 948115824491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115827839","data":{"timestamp":" 948115827839"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115829402","data":{"timestamp":" 948115829402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115834312","data":{"timestamp":" 948115834312"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115835862","data":{"timestamp":" 948115835861"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115840274","data":{"timestamp":" 948115840274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115841843","data":{"timestamp":" 948115841843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115847253","data":{"timestamp":" 948115847253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115848869","data":{"timestamp":" 948115848868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115851621","data":{"timestamp":" 948115851621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115853182","data":{"timestamp":" 948115853182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115856114","data":{"timestamp":" 948115856114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115857714","data":{"timestamp":" 948115857713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115861875","data":{"timestamp":" 948115861875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115863448","data":{"timestamp":" 948115863448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115881556","data":{"timestamp":" 948115881555"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115883149","data":{"timestamp":" 948115883149"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115888293","data":{"timestamp":" 948115888292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115889903","data":{"timestamp":" 948115889903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115897783","data":{"timestamp":" 948115897783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115897872","data":{"timestamp":" 948115897872"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115903844","data":{"timestamp":" 948115903843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.108","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115911002","data":{"timestamp":" 948115911002"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" fa5d6867-b6a8-4251-ade8-1ab0ec7de443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115921157","data":{"timestamp":" 948115921157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-2-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115927413","data":{"timestamp":" 948115927413"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115931912","data":{"timestamp":" 948115931912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115938326","data":{"timestamp":" 948115938326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115944195","data":{"timestamp":" 948115944195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115948653","data":{"timestamp":" 948115948653"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115956892","data":{"timestamp":" 948115956892"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115962787","data":{"timestamp":" 948115962787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115966349","data":{"timestamp":" 948115966348"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 43f526b3-30a0-44e8-ac97-0ac15059ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115977615","data":{"timestamp":" 948115977614"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115984537","data":{"timestamp":" 948115984537"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115986138","data":{"timestamp":" 948115986138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115989538","data":{"timestamp":" 948115989538"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115991094","data":{"timestamp":" 948115991094"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115994502","data":{"timestamp":" 948115994502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948115996061","data":{"timestamp":" 948115996060"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116000613","data":{"timestamp":" 948116000613"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116002168","data":{"timestamp":" 948116002168"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116005885","data":{"timestamp":" 948116005885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116007488","data":{"timestamp":" 948116007487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116010844","data":{"timestamp":" 948116010844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116012434","data":{"timestamp":" 948116012434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116015312","data":{"timestamp":" 948116015312"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116016898","data":{"timestamp":" 948116016898"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116020320","data":{"timestamp":" 948116020320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116021867","data":{"timestamp":" 948116021866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116025276","data":{"timestamp":" 948116025276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116026831","data":{"timestamp":" 948116026831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116030079","data":{"timestamp":" 948116030079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pacha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116031634","data":{"timestamp":" 948116031634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116034076","data":{"timestamp":" 948116034076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116035626","data":{"timestamp":" 948116035626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116038997","data":{"timestamp":" 948116038997"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116040578","data":{"timestamp":" 948116040578"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116044706","data":{"timestamp":" 948116044705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116046715","data":{"timestamp":" 948116046715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116046876","data":{"timestamp":" 948116046876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 67ce6296-c24d-436a-82b4-64335f8ebc1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116056863","data":{"timestamp":" 948116056862"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116057085","data":{"timestamp":" 948116057085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116058058","data":{"timestamp":" 948116058058"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116059340","data":{"timestamp":" 948116059339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116062262","data":{"timestamp":" 948116062261"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116063116","data":{"timestamp":" 948116063115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116063433","data":{"timestamp":" 948116063432"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116064676","data":{"timestamp":" 948116064676"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116068292","data":{"timestamp":" 948116068291"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116069285","data":{"timestamp":" 948116069284"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116069547","data":{"timestamp":" 948116069547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116070505","data":{"timestamp":" 948116070505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116073457","data":{"timestamp":" 948116073457"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116074490","data":{"timestamp":" 948116074489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116074962","data":{"timestamp":" 948116074962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116079549","data":{"timestamp":" 948116079548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116079637","data":{"timestamp":" 948116079637"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" cb7d38c3-79ce-440a-9cc2-3ba3bb4baee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116089058","data":{"timestamp":" 948116089057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116089430","data":{"timestamp":" 948116089430"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116089913","data":{"timestamp":" 948116089912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116090256","data":{"timestamp":" 948116090256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116090659","data":{"timestamp":" 948116090659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116091133","data":{"timestamp":" 948116091133"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116091357","data":{"timestamp":" 948116091357"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116094514","data":{"timestamp":" 948116094514"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116094550","data":{"timestamp":" 948116094550"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116095263","data":{"timestamp":" 948116095263"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116095664","data":{"timestamp":" 948116095664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116095967","data":{"timestamp":" 948116095966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116096174","data":{"timestamp":" 948116096174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116096388","data":{"timestamp":" 948116096387"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116096712","data":{"timestamp":" 948116096711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116096950","data":{"timestamp":" 948116096949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116100108","data":{"timestamp":" 948116100108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116100519","data":{"timestamp":" 948116100519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116103074","data":{"timestamp":" 948116103074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116103285","data":{"timestamp":" 948116103284"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116103500","data":{"timestamp":" 948116103499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116107017","data":{"timestamp":" 948116107016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116110832","data":{"timestamp":" 948116110831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116111867","data":{"timestamp":" 948116111866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116114553","data":{"timestamp":" 948116114553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116114925","data":{"timestamp":" 948116114925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116115408","data":{"timestamp":" 948116115408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116115751","data":{"timestamp":" 948116115751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116116153","data":{"timestamp":" 948116116153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116116626","data":{"timestamp":" 948116116626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116116849","data":{"timestamp":" 948116116849"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116120093","data":{"timestamp":" 948116120093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116120128","data":{"timestamp":" 948116120128"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116120865","data":{"timestamp":" 948116120864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116121266","data":{"timestamp":" 948116121266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116121566","data":{"timestamp":" 948116121565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116121775","data":{"timestamp":" 948116121775"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116121978","data":{"timestamp":" 948116121977"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116122301","data":{"timestamp":" 948116122301"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116122535","data":{"timestamp":" 948116122534"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116125140","data":{"timestamp":" 948116125138"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116125252","data":{"timestamp":" 948116125252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116135277","data":{"timestamp":" 948116135276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 9440d282-831c-403d-891e-257897f1b4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116156354","data":{"timestamp":" 948116156354"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_i_p"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116163808","data":{"timestamp":" 948116163807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_i_p"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116174366","data":{"timestamp":" 948116174366"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_i_p"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116181015","data":{"timestamp":" 948116181015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_p_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116188592","data":{"timestamp":" 948116188592"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_p_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116199098","data":{"timestamp":" 948116199098"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_p_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116205740","data":{"timestamp":" 948116205740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_ch_p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116212388","data":{"timestamp":" 948116212388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_p_ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116219038","data":{"timestamp":" 948116219038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_o_p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116225695","data":{"timestamp":" 948116225695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_y_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116232377","data":{"timestamp":" 948116232376"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_w_z"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116239024","data":{"timestamp":" 948116239024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_h_i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116245690","data":{"timestamp":" 948116245689"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_p_m"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116252354","data":{"timestamp":" 948116252354"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116261366","data":{"timestamp":" 948116261365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" ba42bf6b-5f50-4b66-a448-2a5ff4df6a80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_e_p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116270618","data":{"timestamp":" 948116270618"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116270851","data":{"timestamp":" 948116270850"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116271828","data":{"timestamp":" 948116271828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116273101","data":{"timestamp":" 948116273101"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116276108","data":{"timestamp":" 948116276107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116276975","data":{"timestamp":" 948116276975"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116277295","data":{"timestamp":" 948116277295"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116278541","data":{"timestamp":" 948116278540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116282083","data":{"timestamp":" 948116282082"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116283077","data":{"timestamp":" 948116283077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116283335","data":{"timestamp":" 948116283334"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116284292","data":{"timestamp":" 948116284291"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116287146","data":{"timestamp":" 948116287144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116288191","data":{"timestamp":" 948116288190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116288674","data":{"timestamp":" 948116288674"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116293166","data":{"timestamp":" 948116293165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116293266","data":{"timestamp":" 948116293265"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 3eaf3d98-05e5-440c-9f3c-9e484d0a417f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116305976","data":{"timestamp":" 948116305976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116307896","data":{"timestamp":" 948116307896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116309443","data":{"timestamp":" 948116309443"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116311473","data":{"timestamp":" 948116311473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116313029","data":{"timestamp":" 948116313029"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116316418","data":{"timestamp":" 948116316418"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116317978","data":{"timestamp":" 948116317978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116320124","data":{"timestamp":" 948116320124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116321687","data":{"timestamp":" 948116321687"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116323712","data":{"timestamp":" 948116323712"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116325259","data":{"timestamp":" 948116325259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116329614","data":{"timestamp":" 948116329614"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116331162","data":{"timestamp":" 948116331162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116333398","data":{"timestamp":" 948116333398"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116334955","data":{"timestamp":" 948116334955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116340414","data":{"timestamp":" 948116340414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116341980","data":{"timestamp":" 948116341980"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116345175","data":{"timestamp":" 948116345174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116346727","data":{"timestamp":" 948116346727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116349745","data":{"timestamp":" 948116349745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116351303","data":{"timestamp":" 948116351303"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116353707","data":{"timestamp":" 948116353707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116355266","data":{"timestamp":" 948116355266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116361420","data":{"timestamp":" 948116361420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116362971","data":{"timestamp":" 948116362971"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116370323","data":{"timestamp":" 948116370322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116371884","data":{"timestamp":" 948116371884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116374552","data":{"timestamp":" 948116374551"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116374721","data":{"timestamp":" 948116374721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116381697","data":{"timestamp":" 948116381697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116387746","data":{"timestamp":" 948116387745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116394296","data":{"timestamp":" 948116394295"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" a078e828-b82b-4b61-8b9c-19c8bd348ff3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116403098","data":{"timestamp":" 948116403098"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116405219","data":{"timestamp":" 948116405218"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116407334","data":{"timestamp":" 948116407333"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116410562","data":{"timestamp":" 948116410562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116412812","data":{"timestamp":" 948116412810"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116415075","data":{"timestamp":" 948116415074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116418010","data":{"timestamp":" 948116418009"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116420208","data":{"timestamp":" 948116420208"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116422459","data":{"timestamp":" 948116422458"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116425777","data":{"timestamp":" 948116425777"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116427893","data":{"timestamp":" 948116427893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116430018","data":{"timestamp":" 948116430018"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116432920","data":{"timestamp":" 948116432920"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116435135","data":{"timestamp":" 948116435135"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116437332","data":{"timestamp":" 948116437331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116440279","data":{"timestamp":" 948116440279"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116442600","data":{"timestamp":" 948116442599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116444953","data":{"timestamp":" 948116444953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116447955","data":{"timestamp":" 948116447954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116450086","data":{"timestamp":" 948116450086"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116450550","data":{"timestamp":" 948116450550"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116450629","data":{"timestamp":" 948116450629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 7fe3dcba-9711-4451-8d58-117f818d29ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116505873","data":{"timestamp":" 948116505873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 6258b327-fb3d-40b9-846c-4d00ed5ce953"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_1-13-23"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948116513883","data":{"timestamp":" 948116513882"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_162957"," gameId":" 6258b327-fb3d-40b9-846c-4d00ed5ce953"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_23_1-13-23"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}